[{"id":0,"title":"oh","description":"oug","questions":[{"question":"oiug","rightAnswer":"uigo","wrongAnswer1":"oyg","wrongAnswer2":"oyg","wrongAnswer3":"ogy"}],"avgScore":0.53,"amountPlayed":114},{"id":1,"title":"piuh","description":"ug","questions":[{"question":"ouy","rightAnswer":"uogy","wrongAnswer1":"oyg","wrongAnswer2":"ogyu","wrongAnswer3":"ougy"}],"avgScore":0.3,"amountPlayed":10},{"id":2,"title":"luih","description":"uyg","questions":[{"question":"ouyg","rightAnswer":"uogy","wrongAnswer1":"yf","wrongAnswer2":"oufy","wrongAnswer3":"iytf"}],"avgScore":0.5,"amountPlayed":4},{"id":3,"title":"liug","description":"tiyf","questions":[{"question":"iytf","rightAnswer":"ift","wrongAnswer1":"oufy","wrongAnswer2":"oyfg","wrongAnswer3":"ouf"}],"avgScore":0.25,"amountPlayed":4},{"id":4,"title":"lugy","description":"og","questions":[{"question":"liug","rightAnswer":"igy","wrongAnswer1":"!g","wrongAnswer2":"oyg","wrongAnswer3":"ouyf"}],"avgScore":0.15,"amountPlayed":7},{"id":5,"title":"liug","description":"uyg","questions":[{"question":"ougy","rightAnswer":"oufyv","wrongAnswer1":"oufy","wrongAnswer2":"oufy","wrongAnswer3":"ouyf"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":2},{"id":6,"title":"liug","description":"uyg","questions":[{"question":"ougy","rightAnswer":"oufyv","wrongAnswer1":"oufy","wrongAnswer2":"oufy","wrongAnswer3":"ouyf"}],"avgScore":0.33,"amountPlayed":3},{"id":7,"title":"oufgy","description":"ougy","questions":[{"question":"iluog","rightAnswer":"ogy","wrongAnswer1":"ougy","wrongAnswer2":"ougy","wrongAnswer3":"ougfy"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":8,"title":"liuhb","description":"uyg","questions":[{"question":"yug","rightAnswer":"ogy","wrongAnswer1":"ougy","wrongAnswer2":"ougy","wrongAnswer3":"ougy"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":9,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":10,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":11,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":12,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":13,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":14,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":15,"title":"","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":16,"title":"zada","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":17,"title":"azda","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":18,"title":"azd","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":19,"title":"azda","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":20,"title":"dazda","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":21,"title":"dazda","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":22,"title":"zada","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":23,"title":"dazdaz","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":24,"title":"azdza","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":25,"title":"azdazd","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":26,"title":"dazdazd","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":27,"title":"yjrthz","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":28,"title":"rgzrg","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":29,"title":"jzeg","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":30,"title":"trhzzh","description":"","questions":[{"question":"","rightAnswer":"","wrongAnswer1":"","wrongAnswer2":"","wrongAnswer3":""}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0}]